{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695264973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695264973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695269007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695269007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695270553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695270553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sabuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695274688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695274688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sabuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695276263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695276263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695279555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695279555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695281117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695281117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sungura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695285006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695285006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sungura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695286569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695286569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695289723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695289723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695291302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695291302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sufuria"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695295893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695295893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sufuria"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695297466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695297466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695301542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695301542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695303176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695303175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695305779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695305778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695307398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695307397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695311289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695311288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" START_SWALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695313627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695313627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695315194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695315194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695319320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695319320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695320869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695320869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695324987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695324987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695327002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695327002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695327156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695327156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695612922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695612920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" 4bec25bb-9462-40e2-9a84-89768c700576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695613036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695613035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f23497b2-37f6-4435-86c9-de0c08fa2a3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_68"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tokea siku ile Kalabushe alikoma kuzungumza sana na watu waliokuwa wageni kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695626271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695626271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-u-r"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695629663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695629663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_z-w-s"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695635180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695635180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_z-w-s"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695638700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695638699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_ch-u-s"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695644200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695644200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_f-a-s"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695648125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695648125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-w-p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695652563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695652563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-a-t"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695659462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695659462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_y-e-s"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695662967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695662967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_g-w-s"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695666309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695666309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-g-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695669677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695669677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_h-s-o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695675428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695675426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_s_h-s-o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695681229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695681229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" b27b2c1c-23ab-4eb4-877e-7ec611845ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_s_h-s-o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695690920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695690919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695691301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695691300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695691795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695691795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695692146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695692146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695692563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695692562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695693049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695693049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695693285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695693284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695696539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695696538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695696580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695696580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695697307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695697307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695697701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695697701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695697994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695697994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695698197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695698197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695698390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695698390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695698703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695698703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695698936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695698935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695702175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695702174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695702587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695702586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695705196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695705195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695705406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695705405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695705611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695705611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695709095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695709094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695712908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695712908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695713940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695713939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695716635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695716635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695717020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695717020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695717514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695717514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695717865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695717864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695718278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695718278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695718763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695718762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695718993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695718992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695722167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695722167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695722200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695722200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695722930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695722930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695723335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695723334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695723638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695723638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695723848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695723847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695724048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695724048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695724368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695724368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695724603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695724602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695727200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695727200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548695727273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548695727273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_200727"," gameId":" f2112f61-6ef2-4391-889c-e9976eb0f987"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}